codejava.net 2019-02-27

# CodeJava.net’s Privacy Policy

Details
     Last Updated on 02 November 2013   |  [ Print ](https://www.codejava.net/privacy-policy?tmpl=component&print=1&page= "Print")[ Email](https://www.codejava.net/component/mailto/?tmpl=component&template=protostar&link=0e9eb0750a7acea099cfabdaffb298a29d216a61 "Email")

This Privacy Policy explains what types of information **CodeJava.net** (“CodeJava”, “we”, “us”) may collect from or about visitors to our websites or applications (“you”), and describes our practices for collecting, using and protecting such information.

 **What Personal and Other Information Does CodeJava Collect?**

We may collect personal information and other information from or about you when you:

  *     * Use our website to order products or services.
    * Subscribe to our newsletter program.
    * Make comments on articles.
    * Register to our forum or discussions board.

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “personal information” means information that can be used to personally identify you, such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, user IDs and passwords, billing and transaction information, credit card or other financial information, contact preferences, and similar information.

We also may collect information that is related to you but that does not personally identify you, such as your computer’s operating system, browser, and your use of and activities on our website.

 **How Does CodeJava Use Your Information?**

We may use your personal information and other information for the following purposes:

  *     * To welcome you (such as forum registration, newsletter subscription or product/service orders).
    * To help you complete a transaction or in order to deliver products or services requested by you.
    * To bill you for products or services you purchased.
    * To provide ongoing service and support.
    * To notify you about changes to our website or any products or services we offer or provide through it.
    * To improve our website, services, and products.
    * To e-mail or otherwise send you marketing or other promotional information about **CodeJava** (or its partners) products or services that may be of interest to you.
    * For any other purpose with your consent.

 **How Does CodeJava Protect Your Information?**

 **CodeJava** has implemented administrative, technical, and physical measures designed to protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, disclosure, use, alteration, or destruction.

However, no electronic data transmission or storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% private and secure, and you understand that we do not ensure or warrant the privacy or security of any information we collect from or about you, and that you use our website and other services and provide us with information at your own risk. If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential.

Please also be careful to avoid “phishing” scams, where someone may send you an e-mail that looks like it is from **CodeJava** asking for your personal information. We will never request your personal information through e-mail.

 **Use of Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertising services to display advertisements on **CodeJava** , such as Amazon affiliate program. Some or all of those advertising services may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will send these advertisers information about your visit including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site or [buy finasteride online](http://finasteride.me/buy-finasteride-online.html), and in some cases, whether you have Flash or Java installed. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes. Geo-targeting is sometimes used for the purposes of matching advertisements with visitors based on certain attributes that visitor has. An example of this type of geo-targeting would be showing Idaho movie theatre ads to someone located in Idaho, or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited, such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites.

Deleting cookies does not mean that you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

 **CodeJava** reserves the exclusive right to modify and update this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. We will review and update this Privacy Policy periodically. Therefore, we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy frequently to be informed of how CodeJava.net is collecting, using, retaining, protecting, disclosing, and transferring your information.

If there are any questions, please contact us using the form [here](https://www.codejava.net/contactus), or send us your e-mail to: [webmaster@codejava.net](mailto:%3Ca%20href=).

This Privacy Policy was last updated on October 15, 2013.
